<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Clifford Agius | CA-Software Ltd</title>
    <link>https://cliffagius.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Clifford Agius | CA-Software Ltd</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:23:34 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://cliffagius.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Flying</title>
      <link>https://cliffagius.github.io/top/flying/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:23:34 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cliffagius.github.io/top/flying/</guid>
      <description>Flying and Aviation I will from time to time write a post about aviation and flying the Boeing 787 around the world. I have been asked many times to do this but never really known what to write about, so if you have an idea of a subject you want to hear about the world of Aviation/Flying drop me an email and let me know.
For now here are some nice pictures for you to enjoy&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dot Net 5 Thoughts</title>
      <link>https://cliffagius.github.io/post/dotnet5thoughts/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cliffagius.github.io/post/dotnet5thoughts/</guid>
      <description>.Net 5 Thoughts As .Net5 is just around the corner scheduled release at .Net Conf 2020 which is November 10-12 I thought I would write a bit about my thoughts and what I have found about the up coming changes.
Now these are my thoughts (Hence the name!) but is based on Docs/Blogs/Podcasts/Meet-ups from Microsoft Team members but for the best and latest news take a look at the .Net Downloads Page for the latest release notes and roadmap.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://cliffagius.github.io/top/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 18:46:47 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cliffagius.github.io/top/about/</guid>
      <description>About Me! My Name is Clifford Agius but everyone just calls me Cliff unless I&amp;rsquo;m in trouble that is.
I am an Airline Pilot for a Major UK carrier and I have the fantastic priviledge to fly the Boeing 787 Dreamliner around the world from our home at London Heathrow. This is an amazing aircraft that burns next to no fuel and carries either 217 (-8/-9) or 256 (-10) passengers in comfort at Mach 0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Speaking</title>
      <link>https://cliffagius.github.io/top/speaking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 18:46:47 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cliffagius.github.io/top/speaking/</guid>
      <description>Speaking I am always happy to give talks on Xamarin/IoT especially if it&amp;rsquo;s around projects I am working on, as well as Team Skills from the Aviation world.
You can find my Talks on my Sessionize Speaker Profile
If you interested in having me along at your Meet-Up/Conference/Podcast to talk then please just email me CliffordAgius@CA-Software.Co.uk</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xamarin.Forms NEW Expander Control</title>
      <link>https://cliffagius.github.io/post/xamarinformsexpandercontrol/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cliffagius.github.io/post/xamarinformsexpandercontrol/</guid>
      <description>Xamarin.Forms NEW ExpanderControl Coming along in the new Xamarin.Forms 4.6 release which at the time of writing is at 4.6pre4 (So it&amp;rsquo;s due very soon!) is a new control called the ExpanderControl, now those of you that have played with Web will know this as the Accordian Control in that the user clicks/taps the element in the list and it expands to show more detail of that item.
This control has been added to Xamarin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ideas For a Visual Studio Tool</title>
      <link>https://cliffagius.github.io/post/ideasforvisualstudiotools/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cliffagius.github.io/post/ideasforvisualstudiotools/</guid>
      <description>Idea for a VisualStudio Tool for Xamarin In my last blog I wrote about all the different image sizes required for a Xamarin project and how to calculate them and size them and where to put them, it&amp;rsquo;s all very confusing when you first start out in mobile development so I hope that post helped&amp;hellip;
Recently (2019!) I was working on a standalone UWP project for a new instructor control station in the Mobile Flight Sim I helped to build, this sim is used by the airline I work for at School STEM events, Recruitment and fun corporate events.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Images in Xamarin.Forms </title>
      <link>https://cliffagius.github.io/post/workingwithimagesinxamarin/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cliffagius.github.io/post/workingwithimagesinxamarin/</guid>
      <description>Working with Images In Xamarin Your just starting out developing a Xamarin app and wondering how you add an image, where they go and what sizes are needed. This is something I wondered when I first started and it took me a while to resolve it. The docs Images in Xamarin.Forms are very good (They all are really!) but still I was confused on the best approach. Well I was asked by someone I have been helping a little get into Xamarin Development so rather than just share with one person I thought a blog would be better.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finding and 3D Printing a Hand</title>
      <link>https://cliffagius.github.io/post/findingand3dprintingahand/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cliffagius.github.io/post/findingand3dprintingahand/</guid>
      <description>Finding and 3D Printing a Hand TLDR This is a long post as it&amp;rsquo;s the back story to the whole project and how it came about to getting a design for the hand, it covers the 3D design and printing as well as the problems along the way. Don&amp;rsquo;t worry if your here hoping to see code and electronics or even the Xamarin App thats coming soon, I just need to explain where the Handy design came from first.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Handy the Big Picture!</title>
      <link>https://cliffagius.github.io/post/handybigpicture/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cliffagius.github.io/post/handybigpicture/</guid>
      <description>Handy and the Big Picture Meet Kayden a Local 15 year old and the son of close friends, as you can see he is a happy teenager (They do exist!) full of fun and ready to take on the world&amp;hellip;
 You may also notice that Kayden was born without a left forearm and hand and is also missing the middle fingers on his right hand, so life is a challenge at times but it&amp;rsquo;s Ok the NHS (National Health Service here in the UK) are there to help free of charge (if you conveniently forget you pay TAX).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10 steps to submitting your first Xamarin.Forms PR.</title>
      <link>https://cliffagius.github.io/post/firstxamarinpr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cliffagius.github.io/post/firstxamarinpr/</guid>
      <description>10 steps to submitting your first Xamarin.Forms PR. As a Freelance Xamarin Dev I spend time now and then looking at the Xamarin Github to see if the issue I have been battling with is my code or some bug in Xamarin.Forms or maybe I am trying to work out why something isn&amp;rsquo;t working how I had hoped.
Now I am not saying by any stretch that Xamarin is a buggy code base far from it in the past year or two it has become very stable compared to previous years and yes there are bits here and there (Looking at you UWP!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Custom Fonts and Icons in Xamarin.Forms</title>
      <link>https://cliffagius.github.io/post/customfontsandiconsinxamarin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cliffagius.github.io/post/customfontsandiconsinxamarin/</guid>
      <description>Custom Fonts and Icons in Xamarin.Forms Custom Fonts and using Icons in your project sounds like a lot of work and importing projects like FFImageLoading or Iconize both amazing packages but for this a bit of overkill (if you can get the icons as a font pack!).
So the first job is to get the custom font pack from the design team or the web and we want this in a .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Live Player V Live Reload</title>
      <link>https://cliffagius.github.io/post/liveplayervlivereload/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cliffagius.github.io/post/liveplayervlivereload/</guid>
      <description>Live Player v Live Reload. So, your developing a Xamarin app and getting tired of the make a change, save the change, build the change, deploy the change notice you messed it up so starting the loop over again. Yes that loop can take a few minutes and all you might be editing is the value in the CSS file to change and test the colour of the background (Yes Xamarin.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
