<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Xamarin on Clifford Agius | CA-Software Ltd</title>
    <link>https://cliffagius.github.io/tags/xamarin/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Xamarin on Clifford Agius | CA-Software Ltd</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://cliffagius.github.io/tags/xamarin/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Ideas For a Visual Studio Tool</title>
      <link>https://cliffagius.github.io/post/ideasforvisualstudiotools/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cliffagius.github.io/post/ideasforvisualstudiotools/</guid>
      <description>Idea for a VisualStudio Tool for Xamarin In my last blog I wrote about all the different image sizes required for a Xamarin project and how to calculate them and size them and where to put them, it&amp;rsquo;s all very confusing when you first start out in mobile development so I hope that post helped&amp;hellip;
Recently (2019!) I was working on a standalone UWP project for a new instructor control station in the Mobile Flight Sim I helped to build, this sim is used by the airline I work for at School STEM events, Recruitment and fun corporate events.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Images in Xamarin.Forms </title>
      <link>https://cliffagius.github.io/post/workingwithimagesinxamarin/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cliffagius.github.io/post/workingwithimagesinxamarin/</guid>
      <description>Working with Images In Xamarin Your just starting out developing a Xamarin app and wondering how you add an image, where they go and what sizes are needed. This is something I wondered when I first started and it took me a while to resolve it. The docs Images in Xamarin.Forms are very good (They all are really!) but still I was confused on the best approach. Well I was asked by someone I have been helping a little get into Xamarin Development so rather than just share with one person I thought a blog would be better.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10 steps to submitting your first Xamarin.Forms PR.</title>
      <link>https://cliffagius.github.io/post/firstxamarinpr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cliffagius.github.io/post/firstxamarinpr/</guid>
      <description>10 steps to submitting your first Xamarin.Forms PR. As a Freelance Xamarin Dev I spend time now and then looking at the Xamarin Github to see if the issue I have been battling with is my code or some bug in Xamarin.Forms or maybe I am trying to work out why something isn&amp;rsquo;t working how I had hoped.
Now I am not saying by any stretch that Xamarin is a buggy code base far from it in the past year or two it has become very stable compared to previous years and yes there are bits here and there (Looking at you UWP!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Custom Fonts and Icons in Xamarin.Forms</title>
      <link>https://cliffagius.github.io/post/customfontsandiconsinxamarin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cliffagius.github.io/post/customfontsandiconsinxamarin/</guid>
      <description>Custom Fonts and Icons in Xamarin.Forms Custom Fonts and using Icons in your project sounds like a lot of work and importing projects like FFImageLoading or Iconize both amazing packages but for this a bit of overkill (if you can get the icons as a font pack!).
So the first job is to get the custom font pack from the design team or the web and we want this in a .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Live Player V Live Reload</title>
      <link>https://cliffagius.github.io/post/liveplayervlivereload/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cliffagius.github.io/post/liveplayervlivereload/</guid>
      <description>Live Player v Live Reload. So, your developing a Xamarin app and getting tired of the make a change, save the change, build the change, deploy the change notice you messed it up so starting the loop over again. Yes that loop can take a few minutes and all you might be editing is the value in the CSS file to change and test the colour of the background (Yes Xamarin.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
