<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Xamarin on Clifford Agius | CA-Software Ltd</title>
    <link>https://cliffagius.github.io/tags/xamarin/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Xamarin on Clifford Agius | CA-Software Ltd</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://cliffagius.github.io/tags/xamarin/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>10 steps to submitting your first Xamarin.Forms PR.</title>
      <link>https://cliffagius.github.io/post/firstxamarinpr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cliffagius.github.io/post/firstxamarinpr/</guid>
      <description>10 steps to submitting your first Xamarin.Forms PR. As a Freelance Xamarin Dev I spend time now and then looking at the Xamarin Github to see if the issue I have been battling with is my code or some bug in Xamarin.Forms or maybe I am trying to work out why something isn&amp;rsquo;t working how I had hoped.
Now I am not saying by any stretch that Xamarin is a buggy code base far from it in the past year or two it has become very stable compared to previous years and yes there are bits here and there (Looking at you UWP!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Custom Fonts and Icons in Xamarin.Forms</title>
      <link>https://cliffagius.github.io/post/customfontsandiconsinxamarin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cliffagius.github.io/post/customfontsandiconsinxamarin/</guid>
      <description>Custom Fonts and Icons in Xamarin.Forms Custom Fonts and using Icons in your project sounds like a lot of work and importing projects like FFImageLoading or Iconize both amazing packages but for this a bit of overkill (if you can get the icons as a font pack!).
So the first job is to get the custom font pack from the design team or the web and we want this in a .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Live Player V Live Reload</title>
      <link>https://cliffagius.github.io/post/liveplayervlivereload/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cliffagius.github.io/post/liveplayervlivereload/</guid>
      <description>Live Player v Live Reload. So, your developing a Xamarin app and getting tired of the make a change, save the change, build the change, deploy the change notice you messed it up so starting the loop over again. Yes that loop can take a few minutes and all you might be editing is the value in the CSS file to change and test the colour of the background (Yes Xamarin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Live Player V Live Reload</title>
      <link>https://cliffagius.github.io/post/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cliffagius.github.io/post/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>categories: This is the are to place the post under that is part of the menu at the top so Limited to IOT/XAMARIN/Aviation/Speaking
Tags: These are the tags that get shown on the side menu of the front page of the blog so go wild&amp;hellip;
My First Page This is the first blog page tp check it&amp;rsquo;s all working&amp;hellip;
Images Images go into the /Static/Images folder and get referenced like so?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
